{
    "subject": "resource/Faisal_II_of_Iraq",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Faisal II",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Faisal II of Iraq is Faisal II.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9851813316345215,
            "question": "What is the full name of Faisal II of Iraq?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8902816772460938,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the names 'Faisal I' and 'Faisal II'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8823904395103455,
            "question": "What is significant about the name 'Faisal II'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.860571563243866,
            "question": "Is there more to Faisal II's name than just Faisal II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8467547297477722,
            "question": "Who was Faisal II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8374170064926147,
            "question": "Does the name 'Faisal II' refer to a specific person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6532296538352966,
            "question": "Was Faisal II a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5850033164024353,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any historical figures named Faisal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4662151336669922,
            "question": "Where might one learn more about Faisal II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09120287001132965,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the history of Iraq?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Faisal II of Iraq is Faisal II.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5662_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might one learn more about Faisal II?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5662_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about any historical figures named Faisal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5662_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Faisal II a king?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5662_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5662_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\nThe documents consistently refer to Faisal II by his full name, \"Faisal II\". \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, the full name of Faisal II of Iraq mentioned in one document is indeed Faisal bin Hussein (King Faisal I) and another document mentions Faisal's father as Ghazi and his maternal uncle Prince Abdul Ilah but there are other names and dates provided that suggest he was not simply named 'Faisal II'. However, no information in the documents supports the statement \"The full name of Faisal II of Iraq is Faisal II\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Faisal II, King of Iraq, including his full name as \"Faisal II\" and other details such as his date of birth, reign period, and the end of his monarchy. Therefore, the statement that his full name is Faisal II is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the context information provides Faisal II's full name as \"al-Malik Fay\u1e63al al-th\u0101n\u012b\" (Arabic) and its romanized version, but not as simply \"Faisal II\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}